<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sections on Marion Immo</title>
    <link>http://www.marion-immo.lu/en/sections/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sections on Marion Immo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.marion-immo.lu/en/sections/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Marion Boudier, real estate agent at Re/Max All Stars </title>
      <link>http://www.marion-immo.lu/en/sections/marion-boudier-luxembourg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.marion-immo.lu/en/sections/marion-boudier-luxembourg/</guid>
      <description>Hello, I&amp;rsquo;m Marion, your real estate advisor Re / Max All Stars, the world&amp;rsquo;s leading real estate
Thanks to a thorough knowledge of the market and the support of a vast network, RE / MAX and I can give you valuable advice and provide you with crucial assistance that will ensure the good marketing of your real estate.
I let you discover how we can help you
Please add me tou your phone contacts</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free estimate of your property&#39;s value</title>
      <link>http://www.marion-immo.lu/en/sections/evaluation-bien-immobilier/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.marion-immo.lu/en/sections/evaluation-bien-immobilier/</guid>
      <description>Determining the value of your real estate is the first important step for the sale of the object. This gives you an essential landmark and you know at what price you could sell your real estate on the market.
As an experienced expert in the real estate sector with an exact knowledge of the market, I can give you valuable advice that will guarantee the marketing of your real estate. Contact me by phone and you will receive free and without obligation an expertise of your real estate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pourquoi Re/Max?</title>
      <link>http://www.marion-immo.lu/en/sections/pourquoi-remax/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.marion-immo.lu/en/sections/pourquoi-remax/</guid>
      <description>REMAX International is a real estate organization founded in Denver, Colorado in 1973
RE / MAX is present in 100 countries around the world, including the United States, Canada, and Europe with 40 countries represented
The company is No. 1 in real estate transactions in the World and Europe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pourquoi notre agence?</title>
      <link>http://www.marion-immo.lu/en/sections/pourquoi-remax-all-stars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.marion-immo.lu/en/sections/pourquoi-remax-all-stars/</guid>
      <description>   RE / MAX All Stars in Strassen has been elected :
 1st agency of the REMAX Luxembourg network in 2012, 2013,2015 and 2017 among 14 branches. 2nd agency of the REMAX Luxembourg network in 2014 and 2016 among 14 agencies. Still ranked among the top 100 agencies in Europe on more than 1600 RE / MAX agencies.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Me contacter</title>
      <link>http://www.marion-immo.lu/en/sections/me-contacter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.marion-immo.lu/en/sections/me-contacter/</guid>
      <description> Please call me for more details.
Tél : +352 661 51 06 51
Email : marion.boudier@remax.lu
Web : www.marion-immo.lu
Please, add me to your phone contacts
Please, follow me on youtube    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>